watchingthenet.com 2019-07-16

# Privacy Policy

**  
** THIS IS IMPORTANT — PLEASE READ** **

**GENERAL**  
Watching The Net recognizes that our users have legitimate concerns about privacy with respect to the WTN website. This privacy policy sets forth our practices regarding the collection and use of "personal information" as well as the choices we offer you regarding the use of this information with respect to our website. "Personal Information" is information that personally identifies you, including, for example, your name, address, and Email address.

This policy only addresses our activities from our servers. Other sites (including those that we link to and third party sites or services which we co-brand) may have their own policies, which we do not control, and thus are not addressed by this policy. You provide certain personal information to us when you send Email messages, submit forms or send other information to us. Our servers automatically collect information about which sites users visit and which pages are viewed within the WTN website. We may use a feature of your browser called a "cookie" to assign a User ID that automatically identifies your computer when you visit the site.

We use personal information, among other things, to anticipate and resolve problems with your service, to investigate activity that may violate our Terms of Use and to develop and market products and services that may be of interest to you.

**MISCELLANEOUS**  
We cannot ensure that your private communications and other personal information will not be disclosed to third parties. By way of example, without limiting the foregoing, we may be forced to disclose information to the government under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications.

You can direct any questions concerning these terms to:

_Mike Boyd  
Founder – Watching The Net_  
_wtn (( **at** )) watchingthenet (( **dot** )) com_
